Jasper White is one of those rare people who believe in ancient myths.
He has just bought a new house in the city, but ever since he moved in, he has had trouble with cars and their owners.
When he returns home at night, he always finds that someone has parked a car outside his gate.
Because of this, he has not been able to get his own car into his garage even once.
Jasper has put up 'No Parking' signs outside his gate, but these have not had any effect.
Now he has put an ugly stone head over the gate.
It is one of the ugliest faces I have ever seen.
I asked him what it was and he told me that it was Medusa, the Gorgon.
Jasper hopes that she will turn cars and their owners to stone.
But none of them has been turned to stone yet!